A Guide to the L. Jane Hastings Architectural Papers, 1951-1998, n.d.
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
L. Jane Hastings Architectural Papers, 1951-1998, n.d.
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Hastings, L. Jane
Ms2004-004
10.5 Cubic Feet 8 boxes; 21 oversize folders; 9 boards
Papers of L. Jane Hastings, architect in Seattle, WA, founder and owner of The Hastings Group - Architects. Includes drawings, presentation boards, photographs, and printed material relating to Hastings' professional and design activities.
8 boxes, 21 oversize folders, and 9 boards; 10.5 cu. ft.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The L. Jane Hastings Architectural Papers were donated to the International Archive of Women in Architecture by the creator in 2002.
Biographical/Historical Information
L. Jane Hastings was born and raised in Seattle, Washington. She received a Bachelor of Architecture from the University of Washington in 1952 and became licensed as an architect in the State of Washington in 1953 (she was the eighth woman to do so).
After working for a time in a firm, Hastings started her own practice in 1959. She formed the Hastings Group in 1974, eventually employing eight architects. The Hastings Group carried out work on more than 500 residential projects primarily in the Seattle and surrounding areas. Other projects of the Hastings Group include: small commercial and university facilities remodeling, Sea-Tac Airport renovations, I-90 bridge approach, and historic restoration of an Indian Tribal building.
Hastings' other professional activities include serving as a lecturer in Design Studios in the College of Architecture and Urban Planning at the University of Washington, and as an instructor in the Architectural Drafting Program at Seattle Community College for 10 years. She was also active in various professional organizations, including the American Institute of Architects (AIA) and the International Union of Women Architects (UIFA). She served as the president of the Seattle chapter of AIA in 1975, became a Fellow of AIA in 1980, and served as first woman chancellor of the College of Fellows in 1992.
During the course of her career, Hastings was the recipient of numerous awards and honors for her design work (including the AIA "Home of the Month" Annual Award in 1968), as well as for her other civic and professional activities. Her work was continually featured in the "Home of the Month" and Pictorial Sections of The Seattle Times, as well as in House Beautiful and House & Garden.
Hastings retired from full-time practice in the late 1990s.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Hastings (and, to certain extent, by the other architects of the Hastings Group) in the course of her design and other professional activities. This material primarily comprises drawings, presentation boards, photographs, and printed material, as well as other material, including certificates and plaques. The drawings, presentation boards, and photographs relate to various design projects undertaken by Hastings during the time period from 1959 to 1973 and by the Hastings Group from 1974 to 1998. The printed material includes copies of newspaper and magazine articles that document various completed projects and International Union of Women Architects(UIFA) meeting papers and programs from 1969-1998. Other material includes diploma, license, and awards that document Hastings' professional achievements and honors.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into four series: Series I. Personal Papers, 2009; Series II: Professional Papers, 1951-1997; Series III: Project Records, 1959-1998; Series IV: Art and Artifacts, 1952-1989.
Series I: Personal Papers consists of a biographical outline and a brief history of the drafting tools and processes Hastings has used throughout her career.
Series II: Professional Papers, 1951-1997 consists of material documenting Hastings' numerous professional and civic activities. Newspaper and magazine articles and photographs document various completed residential design projects. Certificates and plaques document Hastings' various professional achievements, including various awards for design and being named a Fellow of the AIA. Other material, such as Hastings' diploma and license, document her entry into the architectural profession. The series is arranged into four subseries: A. Association and Committees, 1969-1998, B. Awards and Other Materials, 1951-1995, C. Reference Files, 1962-1985, 1996-1997, and D. "Home of the Month" residence, 1968-1984.
Series III. Project Records, 1959-1998 consists of material created and accumulated by Hastings (as well as other architects of the Hastings Group) in the course of various design projects. Material includes drawings, presentation boards, and photographs.
Series IV. Art and Artifacts, 1952-1989 consists of 2 registration stamps, a set of drafting tools, a set of lettering tools, four commemorative UIFA scarves, and a miniature book by one of Hastings' clients featuring Hastings' Reed House.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Architectural drawing -- 20th century; International Archive of Women in Architecture (IAWA); Women-owned architectural firms
Genre and Form Terms:
Architectural drawings
Occupations:
Architects
Contents List
- Series I: Personal Papers, 2009, 2015
  - Biographical outline, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "A brief history of L. Jane Hasting's Drafting Days," 2015 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Series II: Professional Papers, 1951-1997, 2009, n.d., This series consists of material documenting Hastings' numerous professional and civic activities including her lifelong involvement in the Union Internationale Des Femmes Architects (UIFA). Newspaper, magazine articles and photographs document various completed residential design projects. Certificates and plaques document Hastings' various professional achievements, including various awards for design and being named a Fellow of the AIA.
  - Subseries A: Associations and Committees, Union Internationale Des Femmes Architects (UIFA), 1969-2004
    - UFIA 1969: Monte Carlo, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - UIFA 1972: Bucarest, Romania, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - UIFA 1976: Iran, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - UIFA 1979: Seattle, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - UIFA 1979: Pacific Coast Tour, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - UIFA 1983: Paris, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - UIFA 1984: Berlin, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - UIFA 1988: Washington, D.C., 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
    - UIFA 1991: Copenhagen, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - UIFA 1993: South Africa, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - UIFA 1996: Budapest, Hungary, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - UIFA 1998: Japan, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - UIFA 2004: France, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper clippings and photographs, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Survey Report, World Congress of Architects-Mexico 1978, Correspondence 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Awards and Other Material, 1951-1995, Includes certificates and plaques for various professional and civic awards received by Hastings throughout her career (including the 2002 AIA Medal of Honor), as well as her diploma from the University of Washington and her architectural license for the State of Washington.
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes certificates and plaques for various professional and civic awards received by Hastings throughout her career, as well as her diploma from the University of Washington and her architectural license for the State of Washington.
    - Diploma, license, and other material, 1951-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Certificates for AIA and other honors, 1965-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15, Box 3)
    - Design awards, 1962-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16, Box 3)
  - Subseries C: Reference Files, 1962-1997, n.d., Includes copies of articles from The Seattle Times, and other newspapers and magazines documenting various design projects, including "Home of the Month" residences. Hastings compiled the articles for submission to the Index of American Women Architects, 1945-1995, she included a completed survey form with each, and organized them alphabetically according to project name. Also includes a copy of Gloria June Peterson's 1996 thesis for the University of Washington entitled Giving Voice: Women in Architecture, Pacific Northwest
    Includes copies of articles from The Seattle Times, and other newspapers and magazines documenting various design projects, including "Home of the Month" residences. Hastings compiled the articles for submission to the Index of American Women Architects, 1945-1995, included a completed survey form with each, and organized them alphabetically according to project name.
    - Articles about various design projects, 1962-1985, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - Research on women architects of the Pacific Northwest, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bound publications, 1981-1991, issues include: Union Internationale Des Femmes Architects, Women in Danish Architecture, Arkkitehteja, UIFA 91 Post Congress Tour of Danish Architecture, UIFA 1981 Workshop, Frauen in Der Architektur Der Gegenwart (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous printed material, 1970-1982, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: "Home of the Month Residences," Photographs and other material, 1968-1984, Includes photographs, negatives, and other material relating to eight of the ten residences designed by Hastings and/or the Hastings Group that were featured in the "Home of the Month" section of The Seattle Times at various times from 1968 to 1984. Files are arranged chronologically (according to how they were organized by Hastings).
    Includes photographs, negatives, and other material relating to eight of the ten residences designed by Hastings and/or the Hastings Group that were featured in the "Home of the Month" section of The Seattle Times at various times from 1968 to 1984. Files are arranged chronologically (according to how they were organized by Hastings).
    - Quam Residence, 176-66, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Schroeder Residence, 188-66, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Rice Residence, 218-68, Whidbey Island, WA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Stevens Residence, 263-71, Tacoma, WA, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Pande Residence, 335-74, Indianola, WA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Jones Residence, 418-77, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Durgin Residence, 458-78, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Reed Residence, 566-83, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Series III: Project Records, 1959-1998, n.d.
  Scope and Content
  The following is a list of architectural projects carried out by Hastings and her firm The Hastings Group.
  Arrangement
  The Project Index is a way to organize the various formats of architectural records from the same project. The index is arranged alphabetically by Project/Client Name and contains information, where available, about the location, date, project type, architect, collaborators, photographers, and formats for each project in the collection.
  Project Index
  A Summary of the Project Index is listed below.
  Project/Client Name (location, date, project type, architect) Collaborator (role), Photographer [Format - Ms=Manuscripts, Dr=Drawings, Ph=Photographs, Sl=Slides, PB=Presentation Boards]
  - Summary of Project Records
    - Akhiok Vehicle Storage Facility (1985; commercial ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Allen Residence, addition and remodeling (1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Allsopp, Mr. and Mrs. Darrell, residence, proposed alterations (1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Alskog Residence, alterations ( 1987-1988; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - American Plywood Association, The Family Circle House That Women Built (1977; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Anderson, Dr. and Mrs. Sam, deck remodel (1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Anderson, Mr. and Mrs. S.D., residence (Tacoma, WA; 1972; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 1)
    - Andrew Residence, remodeling (1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Argens Residence, garage addition ( 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Avriett Residence, Addition and Remodeling ( 1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 1)
    - Baker, R., kitchen - family room addition ( Enumclaw, WA; 1973; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Baker, Russell, addition ( 1959; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Balcom, M., alterations ( Thorp, WA; 1971; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 2)
    - Beale Residence, addition ( 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Bender, Mr. and Mrs. William J., kitchen alterations (1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Berrysmith, D. and F., apartment remodeling (1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Blair and Loustau Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1983; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Bollard, P., proposed kitchen alterations (residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Boisen, Dr. Elliot, addition and remodeling ( 1962; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Boisen, Elliot G., residence ( Edmonds, WA; 1968; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 2)
    - Bolson Residence, addition and remodeling ( Bellevue, WA; 1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Brask, Miss G., addition ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Brown Residence, proposed remodeling ( 1973; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Bryan Residence, proposed alterations ( 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Bryant Residence, addition ( Mercer Island, WA; 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 2)
    - Calhoun,R. Residence, kitchen remodel ( 1993; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Campbell, James T., deck addition ( 1965; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Campbell, Helen, addition and remodeling ( 1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Capital Campus Garage, 1988 ( 1988; government ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Carlson, Frances, proposed office building ( 1974; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Carstrom, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, kitchen remodel ( 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Carter and Gauen Residence, alterations ( 1984/1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Carter Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Cass, Mr. and Mrs. Greg, new residence ( Juanita, WA; 1977; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 3)
    - Chambers/Sparkman Residence, addition/remodeling ( 1990; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Ceci/Chaney, addition and remodel ( 1983; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Chaplin, Mr. and Mrs. David M., kitchen addition ( 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Chisum, Donald, proposed residence ( Hood Canal, WA; 1985; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Christiansen, Mr. and Mrs. James, remodeling ( Bellevue, WA; 1975; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Clarion Company, residence ( Kodiak, AK; 1990; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Clarke, Jon and Dawn, Residence ( 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Clark, M/M John, residence ( Wenatchee, WA; 1993; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Cleland, Robert, addition ( 1971/1977; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 4)
    - Cole, Frank, remodeling ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Cole Residence, alterations ( 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Cole Residence, alterations ( 1988; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Conover, J. addition ( 1965-1968; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Cook, Robert, deck addition ( Monroe, WA; 1968; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Cook, Robert, proposed alterations ( Monroe, WA; 1967; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Coyle, M. Residence, addition/alterations ( 1992; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Cram Residence, alterations ( 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Crawford, C., addition ( 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 5)
    - Crawford, Clyde, chalet ( Snoqualmie Pass [Alpental], WA; 1968; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 5)
    - Creek Residence,remodel ( 1986/1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 6)
    - Crowder, Mr. and Mrs. Paul, proposed residence ( Bellevue, WA; 1968; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 6)
    - Crosetti, Albert H., addition ( 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 6)
    - Crosetti, Albert H., remodeling ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 6)
    - Crystal,Dr. and Mrs. D. K., remodelling ( Mercer Island, WA; 1960; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 6)
    - Curran, L. R. family residence ( 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 6)
    - Darden Residence, remodeling ( 1975; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Darden Residence, addition and remodeling ( Seattle, WA; 1980-1981; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 3, Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 7)
    - Davis, Mr. and Mrs. Charles W., remodeling ( 1975; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Dawson, M/M Gary, kitchen remodeling ( 1994; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Day Residence, alterations ( 1988; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Day Apt - 9B ( 1998; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Deforest,Douglas, alterations ( Bellevue, WA; 1971; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Dietrich Residence, alterations ( 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Divelbiss Residence, additions and remodeling ( 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Dorpat, T. L., addition and remodeling ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Dunn, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph ( 1997; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Durgin, Mr. and Mrs. James ( Seattle, WA; 1979-1980; residential ) [Dr, Sl, Ms] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 7)
    - Dwyer, Mr. and Mrs. R. F., kitchen alterations ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Divyer Residence ( 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Egbert, L. C., addition and alterations ( Kirkland, WA; 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Entrop, Robert, addition ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - L.D. Erickson Condominium #2106 - University Plaza ( 1999; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Eskenazi Residence, addition and remodeling ( Renton, WA; 1983; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 7)
    - Faires, R. G., addition ( 1971; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Felix, Mr. and Mrs. Wm., proposed deck additions ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Finger Residence, remodel ( Kent, WA; 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Flaming Geyser Bridge, Flaming Geyser State Park ( Maple Valley, WA; recreational ) [Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 8)
    - Flohr, Mr. and Mrs. Ned, alterations ( 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Florey, E., addition ( Lake Forest Park, WA; 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Forrester, R. H., proposed plans ( Hansville, WA; 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Fortson, Norval ( 1973/1974; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Fraioli, Jim and Karen, remodeled ( Bellevue, WA; 1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Fremouw Residence, addition and remodeling ( Mercer Island, WA; 1983; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Gaughan, Gerald and Dianne Residence remodeling ( 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Parking Area for Green Lake Funeral Home ( 1962; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Gelfand, Mr. and Mrs. Martin ( Mercer Island, WA; 1974; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 3, Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 8)
    - Gelfand ( Mercer Island, WA; 1992; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Giblin, E. C., summer residence ( Lummi Island, WA; 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Gibson, John and Marilyn, addition and remodeling (residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Gould, J.J., alterations and additions ( 1971; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Gould, J.J., alterations and additions ) ( 1975; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Grayston Residence, alterations ( 1987/1988; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Grayston, Dr. and Mrs. T., Condo #401 ( 1998; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Green Cat Cafe Addition ( 1994; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 8)
    - Haapala, G., addition and alterations ( 1975; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Haapala Residence, additions and remodeling ( 1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hall, Mrs. W. Kal ( Seattle, WA; 1969; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 9)
    - Hampton, Mr. and Mrs. H., alterations to residence ( Bellevue, WA; 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hansen, Roger, addition ( Edmonds, WA; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Harmon Residence, remodeling ( 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Harris, Mr. and Mrs. Dorsey ( Bothell, WA; 1973; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hart, Ms. D-L., storage structure ( Index, WA; 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hastings 916N, personal residence, 1891 house ( Seattle, WA; residential ) [Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 9)
    - Hastings, Douglas, deck addition ( 1963; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hastings, Mr. and Mrs. James C. ( 1963; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hastings, M/M Ralph, addition ( 1991; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hebron Residence, kitchen remodel ( 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hecht, Dwight, alterations ( 1973; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Heglar, George J., Realtors Office Building ( 1961; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hendricks Residence, additions and remodeling ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 9)
    - Hickman, R., addition ( Edmonds, WA; 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Hingston Residence, remodel ( 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Hoffa, Mr. and Mrs. Earl, retreat ( North Bend, WA; 1966; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 10)
    - Hofman, Mr. and Mrs. Dana, residence ( Vashon Island, WA; 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Holland, Mr. and Mrs. K. ( Kodiak, AK; 1978/1979; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 6-7, Oversize 10, Box 6, Box 1)
    - Hollowel, Mr. and Mrs. E., - Owner ( Bothell, WA; 1970; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Hord, Mr. and Mrs. Chas., addition ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Horn, Greg and Mary, additions and remodel ( Sumner, WA; 1980-1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Horwood, Edgar M., carport and addition ( 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 10)
    - Howell, John W. ( Lake Tapps, WA; 1963; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 8, Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 10)
    - Jackson, Mr. and Mrs. Dave, addition ( 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Jacques, Mr. and Mrs. Neal, carport ( 1973; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Jane's Apartment ( reidential ) [Ph] (Box 2, Folder 9, Oversize 11)
    - Johnston, new residence ( Seattle, WA; residential ) [Sl] (Box 6, Box 1, Oversize 11)
    - Johnston, Mr. and Mrs. T. J., retreat ( Hartstene Island, WA; 1973-1974; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 10, Box 3, Box 6, Oversize 11)
    - Jones ( 1979-1980; residential ) [PB, Ms] (Oversize 11, Oversize 22)
    - Karrow Residence ( Seattle, WA; residential ) [Ph, Sl, PB] (Box 2, Folder 11, Box 3, Box 6, Oversize 11, Oversize 29)
    - Karrow, Curt and Marilyn, new residence ( Seattle, WA; 1984; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 11)
    - Keefe, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas ( Bainbridge Island, WA; 1974; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Keiter, F., deck and patio addition ( 1970; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kelly, Mr. and Mrs. William, additions and remodeling ( 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kenmore Family Medical Center ( Kenmore, WA; 1984; medicial ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kenney, Mr. and Mrs. Lyle (1963; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kent, M/M Harold, remodeled residence ( Woodinville, WA; 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kent Residence, garage addition ( Woodinville, WA; 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kinkade ( Vashon Island, WA; residental ) [Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 11)